<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on DevSetGo</title>
    <link>https://devsetgo.com/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on DevSetGo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en_US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 17:57:50 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://devsetgo.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Starlette Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://devsetgo.com/projects/starlette-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devsetgo.com/projects/starlette-dashboard/</guid>
      <description>This project is to serve as an experiment to learn starlette and a basic template for other projects. It is built with the AdminLTE V3.0.1 HTML template
Currently running at stardash.devsetgo.com/   Would love to have help to build a great example for others to use or just fork it for your own use.
Python:
 
CI/CD Pipeline:
  
SonarCloud:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test API a FastAPI Example</title>
      <link>https://devsetgo.com/projects/test-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devsetgo.com/projects/test-api/</guid>
      <description>A test/psuedo API to use as sample data or test data. Inspired by FakeResponse.com. Documentation can be found at devsetgo.com/projects/test-api.
This project is to serve as an experiment to learn FastApi and serve as a useful API to serve psuedo data when needed in other projects.
Currently running at Test-API.DevSetGo.com
 OpenAPI/Swagger UI @ Test-API.DevSetGo.com/docs ReDoc @ Test-API.DevSetGo.com/ReDoc  Python:  
CI/CD Pipeline:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cookiecutter-Flask-SBAdmin</title>
      <link>https://devsetgo.com/projects/cookiecutter-flask-sbadmin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devsetgo.com/projects/cookiecutter-flask-sbadmin/</guid>
      <description>A Flask template for cookiecutter using SB Admin Bootstrap template. Forked from CookieCutter-Flask at version 0.12.0.
This is to have a simpler version using SB Admin as I don&#39;t want NPM or Bower as part of my apps.
Tested with modern Python (3.5 and higher).
Built with cookiecutter
ToDo  Make docker ready deployments Deploy a running example on Docker Clean up of resources to remove unused/needed functionality  Give it a try!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Camunda</title>
      <link>https://devsetgo.com/projects/learning-camunda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devsetgo.com/projects/learning-camunda/</guid>
      <description>Camunda-BPM-Learning Project to store what I learn about Camunda and use for future base projects. Camunda BPM Documents (https://docs.camunda.org) - currently built on v7.9
ChangeLog
Find all Camunda related posts.
Things in the example [0.1.4.5] - 2019-12-11 Added  Added Spring Actuator Enabled all endpoints at /actuator-endpoint Pushed new docker container Updating to Camunda 7.10.0 and SpringBoot Starter 3.2.0 from the November release Update of BPMN processes to use the new Tasklist-startable Process Definitions to prevent processes that should not be the start to be exposed to the WebApp UI  As of 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flask Sufee Admin</title>
      <link>https://devsetgo.com/projects/flask-sufee-admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 -0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devsetgo.com/projects/flask-sufee-admin/</guid>
      <description>Sufee HTML5 Admin Dashboard Template (for Flask!) Sufee is a responsive Bootstrap 4 Admin Template. It provides you with a collection of ready to use code snippets and utilities, custom pages, a collection of applications and some useful widgets. Preview of this awesome admin template available here: https://colorlib.com/polygon/sufee/index.html
 project forked to setup to use in a Flask project.  TOC  Built With Changelog Authors License  Built With  Flask Sass Bootstrap Chart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pynote</title>
      <link>https://devsetgo.com/projects/pynote/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 -0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devsetgo.com/projects/pynote/</guid>
      <description>Journal, Idea Tracker and Other things. This application is based and built off Flask-AppBuilder by dpgaspar
 Run the application from OS Prerequisits
 Python (3.5) virtualenv  Run the application
 create a virtual environment - virtualenv env Install Requirements in Virtual Environment - pip install -r requirements.txt fabmanger create-admin  Follow instructions   fabmanger Run  Application is now running Test and modify code as you want     Run the Application with Docker  Demo version  Docker Pull mikeryan56/pynote_demo:latest demo db  username: admin password: $Password   or clone and run (gunicorn -c gunicorn_cfg.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>